Did you know that if you have a property in Michigan
that you lost to tax foreclosure, it all may not be lost?
I need you to hear this.
When a county takes title to your home or land, April 1st,
for a tax foreclosure, it turns around and has to sell
that property at public auction.
And whoever buys it almost always pays more
than what you owed in taxes.
That difference — that is called surplus.
And it belongs to you, not the government.
It's an obstacle course, though, to get the money back.
You have to file forms, or require a notary.
Eventually, a motion has to be filed in court.
There's a hearing.
It takes almost a year to get those funds.
And that's all I do now — I work with people
so we can get the money back where it belongs.
I would love to work with you, and get that money back in your hands.
Please, feel free — call me.
Text me, send an email, or fill out the form below.
If you lost your Michigan property to a tax foreclosure,
so we can get that money back to you.